This is the Hakimi job search website I created using AI.
The initial version still has a strong AI vibe
but after optimization, it instantly transforms into a dopamine-inducing style
and have compiled it into a step-by-step tutorial to share with you
It is recommended to like and favorite it first
so you won't have trouble finding it when needed
This time we'll directly use Claudecode to create the webpage
Open ClaudeCode and upload Mi's resume
generate a job-seeking website based on the resume
we get a classic blue-purple color scheme
cookie-cutter AI assembly line website
Don't worry
Next, we'll gradually adjust it to a dopamine style.
The first step is to build the framework
Because AI's replication capability far surpasses its imaginative power
before writing the code
You can first build a framework on this website
page layout, where to place buttons and images
first get it clear
then upload the image
Tell the AI 'Write according to this structure'
we get a webpage like this
However, the current color scheme and typography still lack aesthetic appeal and consistency.
We can use Nano banana to unify the website color scheme
upload reference image
Then generate a color palette based on this image
Then let the AI pre-define the spacing and typographic hierarchy of this webpage
maintain page consistency
There is also a skill on GitHub
specifically designed to make our webpage stand out
Combine these three techniques
after several rounds of fine-tuning
we can obtain a dopamine-style webpage
During fine-tuning, use screenshots for communication whenever possible
do not use typing
The more visual information we provide to the AI
the more stable its understanding becomes
For example, this is the text and rounded-corner style I want
upload the screenshot, and ClaudeCode instantly understands
This is much better than using a prompt
say 'make the font on the webpage look good'
The conveyed content is much clearer.
To summarize again
To make the AI-generated page look good
you need to understand at least these 2 principles
First, build the webpage framework and unify the visual style
then write the code
Second, use screenshots as the primary method of communication with AI.
Did you learn it?
Welcome to the Triple Combo
Explore the fascinating world of AI